ngrok.io 2018-10-11

# ngrok - secure introspectable tunnels to localhost

Updated on 9/20/2016

NGROK (referred to here as “we,” “our,” or “ngrok") created this Privacy Policy to inform our website users, customers, browsers, online community participants, those who purchase or inquire about our products and services and others (collectively referred to as “customers”) about our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information (“personal data”) that we collect from them. 

This Privacy Policy is subject to our Terms of Use. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, as specified in the “Changes to This Privacy Policy” section below. 

## Your Consent

You should read this entire Privacy Policy before submitting information to us or using our website. Whenever you submit information via our website or otherwise to us, whether online or offline, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

## Information Collection and Use

We may collect personal data (including, without limitation, age, birthdate, address, email address, phone number, and geographic location) from customers both online and offline. Online, we may collect information through our website or through other online avenues. In many cases, such information will be collected directly from you, such as through registration, a transaction or inquiry (including via a telephone call) or your submission of a form, registration or communication to us. Information may also be gathered from third-party sources, such as third-party service providers, opt-in lists, publicly available data, consumer reporting agencies, other companies and referrals, and through your activities and interactions with us, including, without limitation, your online activity on our website. We may combine data collected from these disparate sources unless we tell you otherwise. 

As you use our website, some information can be “passively” collected using various technologies, such as cookies, web beacons and navigational and location data collection (clickstream, log files, server logs). Your Internet browser automatically transmits some of this information, such as the URL of the website you just visited and the Internet Protocol (IP) address and browser version currently being used by your computer. Such technologies help us to keep track of your interactions with our website and provide you with a more customized experience. 

We use personal data about customers for a wide range of purposes. We use it to respond to your requests; to provide products or services that you have ordered; to process your order transactions and contact you regarding your order; to allow you to post information and other content online; to improve our products and website; to follow up with you after you have communicated with us or submitted information to us; to send promotional communications or offers (unless you have requested that we not send such communications); for marketing, research and legal purposes and other purposes (including, without limitation, call center recordings); to address your interests and concerns; and as otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy and/or at the point of personal data collection. 

We may disclose personal data you provide to consultants, service providers, and contractors that we use to support our business and operations who have agreed to keep the information confidential and use it only to provide the applicable service(s). In some cases, we work with other companies who help to gather information from you or help us to communicate with you. 

We do not share personally identifiable information with third parties for any marketing or commercial purposes. 

We may also disclose personal data to third parties (including, without limitation, governmental agencies) if required to do so by law, regulation or court order; to respond to governmental and/or law enforcement requests; to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with our (or others') rights or property; to support any actual or threatened claim, defense or declaration in a case or before any jurisdictional and/or administrative authority, arbitration or mediation panel; or in connection with disciplinary actions/investigations. We may also disclose personal data to third parties in connection with the sale, assignment or other transfer of the business of our website or the sale, assignment, merger, reorganization or other transfer of our brand or company. 

The recipients of customers’ personal data, and more generally these disclosures, may be located in the United States or other jurisdictions that might not provide a level of protection equivalent to the laws in your jurisdiction. By submitting personal data to us, you consent to the transfer of such personal data outside your jurisdiction. 

We may make full use of all information that is de-identified or otherwise not in personally identifiable form. We may also make full use of all user-generated content you submit to us, in accordance with our Terms of Use. 

## Intended Audience of Websites

Our website is not directed to children under the age of 14. As a result, our website does not request or knowingly collect personal data from individuals under the age of 14. If you are not 14 or older, you should not visit or use our website. 

## Security

We take appropriate steps to protect personal data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction, whether in transmission or storage. Please keep in mind, however, that there is no such thing as perfect security, and no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. Moreover, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any user name and password you use. 

## Contact Preferences; Opt-In and Opt-Out

We would like to keep in touch with you in ways that you find to be beneficial. If you don’t want us to use your contact information to communicate with you for promotional purposes, please tell us that when you provide your contact information. You can also let us know your preference later by clicking on this [link](https://dashboard.ngrok.com/user) and following the instructions on that page or by following the instructions in various communications that we may send you. Keep in mind that these preferences regarding promotional contacts do not mean that we might not contact you for other reasons, such as those related to an order you placed, an inquiry you made, a legally required notice and so on. 

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Do Not Track Notice: Because there are not yet common, industry accepted “do not track” standards and systems, our website does not respond to Do Not Track signals. In addition, we may allow third parties to collect personal data from your activity on our website, as described in the “Information Collection and Use” section above. 

California Disclosure Information: Although we do not disclose to any third parties for their marketing purposes any personally identifiable information, California residents are entitled to receive the following disclosure information under California law: 

Under California Law, California residents have the right to request in writing from businesses with which they have an established business relationship, (1) a list of the categories of personal information, such as name, address, e-mail address, and the type of services provided to the customer, that a business has disclosed to third parties (including affiliates that are separate legal entities) during the immediately preceding calendar year for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, and (2) the names and addresses of all such third parties. We will respond to such written requests within 30 days following receipt at the e-mail address specified below under “Contact Us”. If we receive your request at a different e-mail address, we will respond within a reasonable period of time, but not to exceed 150 days from the date received. Please note that we are required to respond to each customer only once per calendar year. 

## Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns related to this Privacy Policy or our information practices, would like to update or correct information you have provided or would like to opt-out of promotional communications from us, please contact us as follows: [contact@ngrok.com](mailto:contact@ngrok.com)

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time for any reason. If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will include a new effective date, and we will notify you of such changes by posting the revised policy on this page. Be sure to check the Privacy Policy whenever you submit personal data or use our website. The effective date of this Privacy Policy is [insert date].
